<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shrikant Giridhar</title>
    <link>https://gshrikant.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shrikant Giridhar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021, Shrikant Giridhar.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 23:14:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gshrikant.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Session Notes: The Lost Mine</title>
      <link>https://gshrikant.github.io/session-notes-the-lost-mine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 23:14:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gshrikant.github.io/session-notes-the-lost-mine/</guid>
      <description>Date: 23 May 2021 Party  Gregory. Human Cleric (Life) Aaravas. Half Elf. Paladin (Oath of the Ancients) Pio. Half Elf. Rogue (Arcane Trickster)  Summary It was one of our longer sessions (3 hours) and a few interesting events happened.
Last session the party had arrived in Phandalin back from a daring stealth rescue mission. They had managed to infiltrate the Cragmaw tribe&amp;rsquo;s stronghold deep in the treacherous Neverwinter Wood and take out their leader, King Grol, while rescuing their friend Gundren Rockseeker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome (back)!</title>
      <link>https://gshrikant.github.io/welcome-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gshrikant.github.io/welcome-back/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve lost count of the number of times I&amp;rsquo;ve redone my website over the years. This does not include the number of times I&amp;rsquo;ve switched between different blogging platforms and static website hosts. Hopefully, this iteration will last for a bit before I inevitably scrap it in favour of something else.
Welcome back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading List</title>
      <link>https://gshrikant.github.io/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gshrikant.github.io/reading/</guid>
      <description>2021  The Last Wish - Andrej Sapkowski Going Postal - Terry Pratchett  2020  The Black Company - Glen Cook  2019  Rocket Men - Robert Kurson  2018  Bad Blood - John Carreyrou The Three Body Problem - Cixin Liu The Emperor of All Maladies - Siddhartha Mukherjee Small Gods - Terry Pratchett  2016  Being Mortal - Atul Gawande  2015  Hiroshima - John Hershey The Man Who Knew Infinity - Robert Kanigel The Martian - Andy Weir  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
