<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Journal on Shrikant Giridhar</title>
    <link>https://gshrikant.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Journal on Shrikant Giridhar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021, Shrikant Giridhar.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 14:09:53 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gshrikant.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reading B/X</title>
      <link>https://gshrikant.github.io/reading-b/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 14:09:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gshrikant.github.io/reading-b/x/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing a deep-dive into the D&amp;amp;D Moldvay Basic rules in an attempt to learn an old-school fantasy roleplaying ruleset. While my eventual goal is to start a campaign set in a Dying Earth inspired world of my own I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to start small and focus on learning to run a good dungeon-crawl.
I&amp;rsquo;m a late-comer to the world of roleplaying games (RPGs) having started with Call of Cthulhu in the December of 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debugging USB with TinyFPGA BX</title>
      <link>https://gshrikant.github.io/debugging-usb-with-tinyfpga-bx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gshrikant.github.io/debugging-usb-with-tinyfpga-bx/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to write a note on a quick debug session to get my TinyFPGA BX board working with my T450s running Debian Sid (unstable). The board doesn&amp;rsquo;t come with a separate USB controller (typically a FTDI chip or a microcontroller running a USB stack). Instead it loads a bootloader design from its QSPI flash which then presents a CDC class USB device to the host computer which shows up as a /dev/ttyACMn device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session Notes: The Lost Mine of the Mountain King</title>
      <link>https://gshrikant.github.io/session-notes-the-lost-mine-of-the-mountain-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 18:38:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gshrikant.github.io/session-notes-the-lost-mine-of-the-mountain-king/</guid>
      <description>Party Gregory, human Cleric (3) Aaravas, half elf Paladin (3) Pio, half elf Rogue (3) Summary It was one of our longer sessions (3 hours) and a few interesting events happened.
Last session the party had arrived Phandalin back from a daring stealth rescue mission. They had managed to infiltrate the Cragmaw tribe&amp;rsquo;s stronghold deep in the treacherous Neverwinter Wood and take out their leader, King Grol, while rescuing their friend, Gundren Rockseeker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome (back)!</title>
      <link>https://gshrikant.github.io/welcome-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gshrikant.github.io/welcome-back/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve lost count of the number of times I&amp;rsquo;ve redone my website over the years not to mention the number of times I&amp;rsquo;ve switched between blogging and static website hosting platforms. Hopefully, this iteration can hang around for a while before I inevitably scrap it in favour of something else. Welcome back!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
